<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
   New Perspectives on XML 3rd Edition
   Tutorial 6
   Tutorial Case

   Harpe Gaming Store Products
   Author:
   Date:

   Filename:         products.xml
   Supporting Files: products.xsl

-->

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="products.xsl" ?>

<products>
    <product pid="vg10551">
        <title>Dance Off VII</title>
        <manufacturer>Anasta Games</manufacturer>
        <price>29.95</price>
        <releaseDate>2017-09-28</releaseDate>
        <media>Video Game</media>
        <image>images/dance_off.jpg</image>

        <summary>
            <h3>Challenge Yourself with Dance</h3>

            <p>
                Bryan, a movie enthusiast since childhood, started a blog to share his passion for films while juggling
                a day job. His authentic and relatable reviews attracted a growing audience, leading to offers for
                collaborations and sponsorships. Despite opportunities, Bryan prioritized maintaining the authenticity
                of his blog, staying true to his love for storytelling through movies.
            </p>
        </summary>

        <reviews>
            <review>
                <title>My favorite workout video and workout game</title>
                <text>I've owned all the Dance off releases from the beginning. It's my favorite workout video every
                    morning. I have lost 12 pounds with very little modification of my diet. Dance off just gets better
                    with every release. The song tracks are greate. There is a wonderful selection of new and old tracks
                    from around the world. some obscure and others more popular, including several that are in heavy
                    rotation on the radio right now. Most tracks have several choreographic alternatives that can be
                    unlocked by earning in-game dance points.
                </text>
                <writer>Maria Smantha</writer>
                <place>Galway, New York</place>
                <date>November 18, 2017</date>
                <stars>2</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>Poor choreography</title>
                <text>A so-so release of this well-established title. The user interface is improved and easier to use
                    and game provides a few great songs, a few terrible ones, and several mediocre ones. The graphics
                    are beautiful and the sets are stunning and fun (without being distracting) Where this release fails
                    is in the choreography. The dances just aren't as much fun as the previous titles. Many of the moves
                    follow predictable patterns; they're stale and that's a big problem for a dance game. I hope the
                    next release improves the choreography because it's great in all other phases of the game.
                </text>
                <writer>Lisa Cudrow</writer>
                <place>Sea Island, Georgia</place>
                <date>November 14, 2017</date>
                <stars>4</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>Can love be rekindled despite the competition</title>
                <text>Some nice terpsichorean talent is on full display in Dance Off. Some talented dancing young people
                    put this across and you don't mind the plot which involves a reunion of sorts between childhood
                    sweethearts now rivals at different dance studios. Can love be rekindled between Shane Harper and
                    Kathryn McCormick despite the competition. People around both Harper and McCormick are urging both
                    to get a mean on in regard to the competition. But amateur dancers Harper and McCormick prove
                    they're professional enough. There's a sub plot going on between David Burtka a former dancer
                    himself and his Devil Wears Prada mother Carolyn Hennessy who is running the "National Nationals"
                    competition. I swear that's the name. Although you get the idea you are watching an extended version
                    of the Disney Studio show Shake It Up, the talented and appealing young people make this an easy to
                    take musical film.
                </text>
                <writer>bkoganbing</writer>
                <place>Galway, New York</place>
                <date>August 31, 2015</date>
                <stars>2</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>Had potential but somewhat flopped in the end</title>
                <text>The acting and the plot were somewhat lackluster. I wondered at times what genre of film I was
                    watching and found myself confused as the story skipped over many details that could of really
                    improved the movie. However, I was shocked at how good the dancers were. The dance shots were
                    beautiful and somewhat made up for the fact that the story left me with so many questions. A good
                    watch if you need something light with some nice visuals.
                </text>
                <writer>jhhox10</writer>
                <place>Atmore, Alabama</place>
                <date>November 14, 2015</date>
                <stars>4</stars>
            </review>
        </reviews>

    </product>
    <product pid="vg10552">
        <title>Net Force 12</title>
        <manufacturer>Nitta Sports</manufacturer>
        <price>35.72</price>
        <releaseDate>2017-10-03</releaseDate>
        <media>Video Game</media>
        <image>images/net_force.jpg</image>
        <summary>
            <h3>Take the Battle to the Hardwood</h3>
            <p>
                Net Force 12
                is the latest release in the Net Force series of basketball
                simulation games. Using motion capture technology designed specifically for
                Net Force, this release captures the signature moves of the top players in
                the NBA, No other basketball simulation has this lineup of stars. Additional
                features include support for motion-sensor game controllers, dynamic shot
                generation, touch-sensitive passing, and "flash-to-the-hoop" acceleration
                for uncontested slam dunks.
                Go to basketball camp and learn the game the right way with a series of fun
                and challenging tutorials. Relive the past with stars from the 60's, 70's, 80's,
                and 90's. Can today's stars hold their own against the champs from the past?
                You decide.
                Take your virtual game to a new entertainment level with the dynamic background
                music and production by some of the top hip-hop artists on the charts. Previous
                releases of Net Force have already won multiple awards for music and
                production and this release looks posed to continue that winning streak.
            </p>
        </summary>

        <reviews>
            <review>
                <title>The Facts.</title>
                <text>Made for tv movies can never escape the feeling they're made for television. The taste, the sight
                    and the scent. It's always there. Tom Clancy's Netforce itself was originally a two part television
                    movie (how little did I know). In fact, it's all still somewhat a wash. Let me break it down for
                    you. Flash forward to 2005. The internet has become so powerful and potentially dangerous that the
                    US government sets up a division within the FBI entitled "Netforce" to preside over it from the evil
                    people of the world who look to exploit it for their corrupt plans. Personally I seriously
                    disbelieve the internet holds the future of the world in it's grasp, but that doesn't matter because
                    the people at Netforce couldn't protect it if they had to anyway. Upon meeting the major characters
                    we realize they're roles we've all seen before. Like the male main character who's strong and
                    dresses well. The rest of the cast fit typical molds. I especially liked how a certain character's
                    ex-wife is a news reporter who at one point becomes a key piece in the story. Everyone is so linked
                    together. Realistic? No. Then again none of the characters have any real depth. They're just names
                    and faces. There's also too many needless minor characters who provide nothing but padding and
                    viewer confusion. It gets hard remembering twenty characters throughout a two plus hour movie. I
                    want to give credit for trying to develop them, but it fails because we know they're insignificant.
                    Frankly I expected more from such an ensemble cast too. Scott Bakula gets to look smart in suit, but
                    this could have benefited from someone with more clout than Bakula. He's sufficient, but that's
                    about it. Meanwhile Kris Kristofferson gets the cliché elder role and good 'ol Brian Dennehy has
                    been given the plum task of the President's Chief Of Staff. That means him popping up spewing 'How
                    his ass is on the line' or 'the President's p***ed at him'. Yes good actors can't save bad scripts.
                    That's a fact. Which bothers me even further because this product has Tom Clancy's name written all
                    over it. Yet it isn't anywhere near the quality of his past outings. It's a real disservice. Some of
                    the blame has to fall straight into the writer's lap too. I say this because I find it hard to see
                    this as an adaptation project that started well. It was bad from the get-go. The story stinks. It's
                    amateur hour. Especially considering how much they squeeze into their time frame. Would more have
                    helped? I'm hesitant to say. Even with over two hours they still came back with this slop. Frankly
                    160 minutes is a long time and there isn't enough depth to sustain a person's interest or the
                    holding of disbelief for such a period. It can't even be taken seriously. Like Judge Reinhold
                    playing the 'evil multi-billion dollar software tycoon' looking to control the world or how corny it
                    is to have FBI agents point loaded weapons in the faces of innocent cabdrivers. It's things like
                    these that help make Netforce such a bore and honestly for a film dealing so heavily with computers
                    and the internet, they sure went skimpy on the technical aspects too. I guess they didn't want to
                    lose their biggest viewing demographic ... computer inept coach potatoes and patriotic Tom Clancy
                    fans. For what it's trying to be, NetForce offers very little (if any) paranoia, suspense or "edge
                    of your seat excitement" as so called critics would say. Netforce draws nothing but boredom and
                    that's not exactly new territory. Last thing too. A golden rule of movies. If they don't find a body
                    95% of the time that's a clear signal the person ain't dead. That's the facts.
                </text>
                <writer>refinedsugar</writer>
                <place>Arizona, Ajo</place>
                <date>6 July 2001</date>
                <stars>4</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>Takes itself WAY too seriously</title>
                <text>For a film based upon such a refined subject as computers and the intricacies of the internet, I
                    felt sure that there'd have to be some sort of off-the-cuff humour injected somewhere during
                    proceedings to offset the technical detail. Surely they couldn't expect everybody to get excited
                    about firewalls, web browsers and computer crime without something else to keep it company. Well, as
                    it turns out, that's exactly what they expected and the film turns out to be drier than dust. Some
                    of the technical detail was stretched to the very limit of credibility - it seems they severely
                    overshot what the internet would be like in 2005 - yet they still imagined we'd be using floppy
                    disks? More research, and effort, was called for in places that's for sure. Plus, it was an hour too
                    long. Nearly 160 minutes is far too excessive for a film of its kind and an hour could easily have
                    been taken off without too many problems. The acting was hokey - but not as bad as some TV movies -
                    the technology very dodgy in parts and the romance subplot extremely wobbly, but anybody with even
                    half an interest in computers and the internet may as well give it a go.
                </text>
                <writer>neil_mc</writer>
                <place>California, Alameda</place>
                <date>6 October 2005</date>
                <stars>2</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>To long and too dull</title>
                <text>Scott Bakula (Quantum Leap's Sam Beckett) and Kris Kristofersson (Blade, Pat Garett and Billy the
                    Kid) star in this below average TV movie. It seems quite a lot of money (for a TV movie) has been
                    thrown at this but the pace at times is down to a crawl and Bakula's character seems to have become
                    head of Netforce with a total lack of any computer knowledge. It's dated fairly badly but all movies
                    about computers do that look at Wargames or Tron! But its main problems are down to a flabby script,
                    pedestrian direction and lack of tension as for the ending i'm not even going to go there! Let's
                    just say it ain't great, I gave this film a 4/10 as it's not a total lost cause but i cant recommend
                    spending 2+hours watching this when there are better films out there. If you want a hacker movie War
                    Games (Mathew Broderick) or Sneakers (Robert Redford, River Phoenix) are better movies in the same
                    sort of area or for a more MTV friendly teen hacker movie then go for Hackers (Angelina Jolie &amp;
                    Tommy Lee Miller). 4/10 - If there's nothing better on a rainy Sunday it might pass the time but
                    thats about all, we can only hope the Quantum Leap movie gets off the ground to save Scott Bakula!
                </text>
                <writer>no-skyline</writer>
                <place>California, Anaheim</place>
                <date>29 October 2007</date>
                <stars>5</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>humorously poor</title>
                <text>This movie is actually pretty watchable if you are a bit technical and don't mind viewing a film
                    to laugh at its inherent badness. The script repeatedly uses networking lingo out of context and
                    demonstrates a fundamental lack of understanding of networking principles. My favorite scene is when
                    they're searching logs for traces of a computer break-in and the hero exclaims when no traces are
                    found "There's not even a cookie?!?". I expect even a non-tech should be able to find a couple of
                    laughs about the overwhelming lack of technical advisement. Some understanding of distributed
                    attacks and viruses might have helped, but I guess the idea of two hackers trying to out type each
                    other works better for Hollywood. The cinematography is low-average for a made for TV. I liked Judge
                    Reinhold's acting, and Kris Kristofferson, Bakula I found to be often flat or alternately overacted.
                    Conclusion: Don't rent it unless you're into bad movies, worth catching on Cable on a slow day.
                </text>
                <writer>DrK0H</writer>
                <place>Colorado, Alamosa</place>
                <date>13 June 2004</date>
                <stars>4</stars>
            </review>
            <review>
                <title>humorously poor</title>
                <text>This movie is actually pretty watchable if you are a bit technical and don't mind viewing a film
                    to laugh at its inherent badness. The script repeatedly uses networking lingo out of context and
                    demonstrates a fundamental lack of understanding of networking principles. My favorite scene is when
                    they're searching logs for traces of a computer break-in and the hero exclaims when no traces are
                    found "There's not even a cookie?!?". I expect even a non-tech should be able to find a couple of
                    laughs about the overwhelming lack of technical advisement. Some understanding of distributed
                    attacks and viruses might have helped, but I guess the idea of two hackers trying to out type each
                    other works better for Hollywood. The cinematography is low-average for a made for TV. I liked Judge
                    Reinhold's acting, and Kris Kristofferson, Bakula I found to be often flat or alternately overacted.
                    Conclusion: Don't rent it unless you're into bad movies, worth catching on Cable on a slow day.
                </text>
                <writer>DrK0H</writer>
                <place>Colorado, Alamosa</place>
                <date>13 June 2004</date>
                <stars>4</stars>
            </review>
        </reviews>

    </product>
</products>